{
    "subject": "resource/Joe_Jonas",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Joe Jonas was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872621893882751,
            "question": "Was Joe Jonas born in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8534185886383057,
            "question": "Where was Joe Jonas born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8495643138885498,
            "question": "Is Joe Jonas American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6948423385620117,
            "question": "What is Joe Jonas's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846380591392517,
            "question": "Where did Joe Jonas originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5114745497703552,
            "question": "What is Joe Jonas's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4323810338973999,
            "question": "What country is Joe Jonas from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41483378410339355,
            "question": "In which nation did Joe Jonas come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3856586515903473,
            "question": "Joe Jonas hails from which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3521263897418976,
            "question": "To which country does Joe Jonas belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joe Jonas was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9242_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joe Jonas hails from which country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9242_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation did Joe Jonas come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9242_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Joe Jonas from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9242_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9242_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Joe Jonas was born on August 15, 1989, in Casa Grande, Arizona. Casa Grande is a city in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Joe Jonas was born in the United States\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}